A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Minutes and Annual Reports, SG 16.1 and SG 16.2 FA120
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Minutes and Annual Reports, SG 16.1 and SG 16.2
1913-1991
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA120
66.45 Cubic Feet 38 microfilm boxes (35mm), 34 record storage boxes, and 56 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
User copies of minutes microfilm are open for research. Access to the original published volumes of annual reports is permitted.
Scope and Contents
The microfilm contains minutes of the Foundation.
Arrangement
This record group is arranged in two subgroups.
Subgroup 16.1 - Minutes. Subgroup 16.2 - Annual Reports.
Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Philanthropy; Charities; Life sciences; Philanthropy -- United States; Public health; Arts; Medical sciences; Humanities
- Rockefeller Foundation Minutes, 1913-1987; 1; 21.77 Cubic Feet 38 microfilm boxes (35mm) and 56 letter document boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation Minutes (Microfilm), 1913-1987; 1; 0.5 Cubic Feet 38 microfilm boxes (35mm)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Board of Trustees minutes more than 20 years old are open for research. Microfilm user copies are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
    - Minutes, 1913-1946 (Reel 1)
    - Minutes, 1947-1964 (Reel 2)
    - Minutes, 1913-1918 (Reel 3)
    - Minutes, 1919-1922 (Reel 4)
    - Minutes, 1923-1925 (Reel 5)
    - Minutes, 1926-1927 (Reel 6)
    - Minutes, 1928-1929 (Reel 7)
    - Minutes, 1930-1931 (Reel 8)
    - Minutes, 1932-1934 (Reel 9)
    - Minutes, 1934-1936 (Reel 10)
    - Minutes, 1937-1939 (Reel 11)
    - Minutes, 1939-1941 (Reel 12)
    - Minutes, 1942-1944 (Reel 13)
    - Minutes, 1945-1947 (Reel 14)
    - Minutes, 1948-1949 (Reel 15)
    - Minutes, 1950-1951 (Reel 16)
    - Minutes, 1952-1953 (Reel 17)
    - Minutes, 1954-1955 (Reel 18)
    - Minutes, 1955-1956 (Reel 19)
    - Minutes, 1957 (Reel 20)
    - Minutes, 1958 (Reel 21)
    - Minutes, 1959 (Reel 22)
    - Minutes, 1960 (Reel 23)
    - Minutes, 1961 (Reel 24)
    - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Reel 25)
    - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Reel 26)
    - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Reel 27)
    - Minutes, 1966-1968 (Reel 28)
    - Minutes, 1968-1969 (Reel 29)
    - Minutes, 1970-1971 (Reel 30)
    - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Reel 31)
    - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Reel 32)
    - Minutes, 1975-1976 (Reel 33)
    - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Reel 34)
    - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Reel 35)
    - Minutes, 1980-1982 (Reel 36)
    - Minutes, 1983-1985 (Reel 37)
    - Minutes, 1985-1987 (Reel 38)
  - Board Minutes and Grant Memos (Paper), 1913-1987; 2; 21.27 Cubic Feet 56 letter document boxes
    - Indexes, 1913-1946, 1965-1986 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1913-1916 (Box 3)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1917-1922 (Box 4)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1923-1925 (Box 5)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos -1926-1927 (Box 6)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1928-1929 (Box 7)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1930-1931 (Box 8)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1932-1933 (Box 9)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1934-1935 (Box 10)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1936-1937 (Box 11)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1938-1939 (Box 12)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1940-1941 (Box 13)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1942-1943 (Box 14)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1944-1945 (Box 15)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1946-1947 (Box 16)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1948-1949 (Box 17)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1950-1951 (Box 18)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1951-1952 (Box 19)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1953-1954 (Box 20)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1954-1955 (Box 21)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1955-1956 (Box 22)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1956 (Box 23)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1957 (Box 24, Box 25)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1958 (Box 26, Box 27)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1959 (Box 28)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1960 (Box 29)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1960-1961 (Box 30)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1961 (Box 31)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1962 (Box 32)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1963 (Box 33)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1964 (Box 34)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1965 (Box 35)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1966 (Box 36)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1967 (Box 37)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1968 (Box 38)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1969 (Box 39)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1970 (Box 40)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1971 (Box 41)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1972 (Box 42)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1973 (Box 43)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1974 (Box 44)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1975 (Box 45)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1976 (Box 46)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1977 (Box 47)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1978 (Box 48)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1979 (Box 49)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1980 (Box 50)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1981-1982 (Box 51)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1982-1983 (Box 52)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1984 (Box 53)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1985 (Box 54)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1986 (Box 55)
    - Board Minutes and Grant Memos - 1987 (Box 56)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Reports, 1979-1982, 1985-1987, 1989-1991; 2; 8 Bound Volumes
  Annual reports
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1979 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1979)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1980 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1980)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1981 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1981)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1982 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1982)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1985 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1985)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1986-1987 (Item REF 362.763 2 ROC 1986-87)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1989 (Item REF 3610763 2 ROC 1989)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1990 (Item REF 361.763 2 ROC 1990)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report 1991 (Item REF361.763 2 ROC 1991)